<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

 <title>Sam's Skunkpit</title>
 <link href="http://gamesketches.gitpages.io/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="http://gamesketches.gitpages.io/"/>
 <updated>2015-03-10T10:33:58-04:00</updated>
 <id>http://gamesketches.gitpages.io</id>
 <author>
   <name>Sam Von Ehren</name>
   <email>sam.von.ehren@gmail.com</email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>Street Fighter III, 2nd Impact vs 3rd Strike part 2</title>
   <link href="http://gamesketches.gitpages.io//2015/03/09/3rd-strike-second-impact-2/"/>
   <updated>2015-03-09T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>http://gamesketches.gitpages.io/2015/03/09/3rd-strike-second-impact-2</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I wanted to build on my last post a little bit more and talk about some of the in-battle aesthetic differences between Street Fighter 3: 2nd impact and it’s younger brother Street Fighter 3: 3rd Strike. You can find my comparison of their character select screens &lt;a href=&quot;http://gamesketches.github.io/2015/02/24/3rd-strike-second-impact/&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The differences between gameplay visuals follow the same theme from the character select screens. 2nd Impact takes a lot of influence from mid-90s Capcom fighters, while 3rd Strike is a little more stylistic. However, while preparing this post, I found I preferred some ideas from 2nd impact over 3rd strike. With the character select screens, there’s no contest, 3rd Strike’s bleeds style out of the screen and into the player’s eyeballs. Once in battle though, I think 3rd Strike’s push towards minimalism actually hurts the visual experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;2nd Impact&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;3rd Strike&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://gamesketches.gitpages.io/images/2iBackground.png&quot; alt=&quot;2iBackground&quot; /&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://gamesketches.gitpages.io/images/3sBackground.png&quot; alt=&quot;3sBackground&quot; /&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Street Fighter III, 2nd Impact vs 3rd Strike</title>
   <link href="http://gamesketches.gitpages.io//2015/02/24/3rd-strike-second-impact/"/>
   <updated>2015-02-24T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://gamesketches.gitpages.io/2015/02/24/3rd-strike-second-impact</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I was trolling around on youtube today when I came across some footage of Street Fighter 3: 2nd Impact. As a big fan of 3rd Strike, I was interested in seeing an earlier iteration of a game I loved. After watching, I was surprised at how stylistically different 2nd impact is. While the character sprites and core gameplay are basically the same, the aesthetic is completely different.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First a little explainer for those not versed in Street Fighter, SF3 was one of the last fighting games released by Capcom before the “drought” of the aughts. There were three iterations of SF3 each with a different sub-title: “New Generation”, “2nd Impact”, and “3rd Strike” respectively. New Generation and 2nd Impact were both released in 1997, then in 1999 Capcom released 3rd Strike, the last Street Fighter game til SF4 came out in 2008. From what I’ve seen of 2nd Impact, it seems like those two years were spent totally revamping the game’s visuals and audio design into something cohesive and new.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From what I can tell, New Generation and 2nd Impact were designed in the same visual idiom as Capcom’s other mid 90s games, easily exemplified by the [Vs Series](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Marvel_vs.&lt;em&gt;Capcom&lt;/em&gt;(series) and the Alpha series(&lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Street_Fighter_Alpha_3&quot;&gt;Alpha 3&lt;/a&gt; was released just a year after 2nd impact). This idiom is fine but is so starkly different compared to 3rd strike. I think the character select screens are a pretty good launching point so I’ll start there. First let’s take a look at the 2nd Impact screen. Here’s a clip which features the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yOZuaz2Lnbc#t=48&quot;&gt;2nd impact character select screen&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first thing that jumped out to me when I saw this was just how washed out all the colors are. The palettes for each character are very very light and the shading is done in huge, obvious blocks. The minimal shading is made worse by the spotlight shining on each character’s body. I’m guessing that’s supposed to be the light from the middle of the screen but the blockiness of the shading just makes the colors seem off. For example, the whole left side of ryu’s face is basically pure white, it’s kind of comical and very cartoony. The thickness of the lines further emphasizes the cartoon look. Finally, this is a little subjective but I also the character’s poses make them look goofy and weak. Specifically, Necro looks like he’s deep in thought, Ibuki looks tentative, Urien looks like he’s going for a drug addled fist bump, Elena is doing stretches, and Oro is about to lose his lunch. These would be great with a puzzle fighter aesthetic but seem odd in a core Street Fighter game.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The second thing I notice is the music. The music is bizarrely cheery and flat (like soda, not pitch). It’s the kind of generic music I’d expect to see in an obscure Japanese shmup (&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uxv5A3xZnm8&quot;&gt;Area 88&lt;/a&gt; for example), not in a main stream fighting game and DEFINITELY not in the precursor to 3rd Strike. Part of that lack of depth is just sound quality, but after listening carefully to 3rd strike’s music, I think the real issue is that there is no real attempt at hiding how lo-fi the sound is. It’s just a simple melody with a little background harmony and drum fills.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next, let’s talk about the actual sound effects. The sound effect for cursor movement is this high pitched ping sound that I’d expect in a movie about bomb disposal. It’s such an odd choice for the action. To me it makes the menu feel like some high tech interface. This also plays into the Japanese shmup thing I mentioned with the music. When you select a character, there’s a sort of heavy bass drum and then a high note. This sound isn’t too bad, it’s a lot more impactful than the movement sound, but I don’t think it pops the way it should.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then there’s the announcer. The announcer sharply contrasts everything else. It’s this deep gravely voice that calls out your character name. I do think the 3rd Strike announcer is better, but this is one part I’m okay with. The announcer doesn’t mesh well with the other elements but on his own he’s not bad.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now let’s compare all these elements with their 3rd strike counterparts. Here’s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Vz4d2Gl3NbM#t=50&quot;&gt;3rd Strike’s character select&lt;/a&gt; for comparison.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First thing again is the character portraits. The use of lighting/shading is so much more sophisticated in these portraits. There’s clearly a light above them, and while there’s some of the extreme brightness it’s used so much more economically it gives the portraits a ton of depth. 3rd strike also opts to focus the portraits on the face rather than torso. This choice emphasizes personality and intimacy, making the characters seem much stronger. Oro and Necro are particularly improved, each looking at the “camera” with menacingly blank expressions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The music while kind of muted is substantially more complicated. Instead of a simple melody, there’s hip-hop artist &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ghetto_Concept&quot;&gt;Infinite&lt;/a&gt; rapping with a sax, drum, and base line with strings holding out notes over everything. I believe the sound chip is the same but the way the tracks are layered hides the fidelity from the listener, making the aural experience seem deeper and more engaging.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then there’re the sound effects. The first thing to notice is the movement sound effect. It’s this amazing, deep, toggling sound. It almost sounds like a pipe hitting the ground. It’s hard to describe and very unique. When you actually select a character you get a deep bass drum type sound, as in 2nd Impact, and then the Announcer calls out to you “Woah, I got the picture!”, when you select your super he says “Yeah, I’ve been waiting for this!”. Such an interesting dynamic emerges from this change. When picking your character, the game is gets buddy buddy with you, slink up next to you because it’s excited to see your match. I think this is substantially more engaging than 2nd Impact’s character select screen. It creates a feeling of going somewhere underground (like an arcade!) for some fighting. It’s compelling and engaging.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s all for now, I’ll probably write more about this and focus on some of the in game aesthetic differences.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>My first real post</title>
   <link href="http://gamesketches.gitpages.io//2015/02/16/the-first-post/"/>
   <updated>2015-02-16T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://gamesketches.gitpages.io/2015/02/16/the-first-post</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Here’s my first real attempt at a post. I’ve been meaning to start a real personal website for awhile. When I learned that github did website/blog hosting I hopped on pretty immediately. The name gamesketches comes from my &lt;a href=&quot;http://gamesketches.wordpress.com&quot;&gt;old blog&lt;/a&gt;. I picked it because I was working on rapid prototyping. I thought about reviving it but I’m very into ditching blogs if I haven’t updated them in awhile. I also wanted to have a website where I would have a little more freedom and control over the content. I hope to update this blog frequently with talk about games (particularly video, but any games I find interesting), mixology, and anything else I find interesting, so please stick around and enjoy.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Introducing Poole</title>
   <link href="http://gamesketches.gitpages.io//2014/01/02/introducing-poole/"/>
   <updated>2014-01-02T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://gamesketches.gitpages.io/2014/01/02/introducing-poole</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Strange Case of Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Hyde&lt;/em&gt; tells the story of a lawyer investigating the connection of two persons, Dr. Henry Jekyll and Mr. Edward Hyde. Chief among the novel’s supporting cast is a man by the name of Mr. Poole, Dr. Jekyll’s loyal butler.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Poole is the butler for &lt;a href=&quot;http://jekyllrb.com&quot;&gt;Jekyll&lt;/a&gt;, the static site generator. It’s designed and developed by &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/mdo&quot;&gt;@mdo&lt;/a&gt; to provide a clear and concise foundational setup for any Jekyll site. It does so by furnishing a full vanilla Jekyll install with example templates, pages, posts, and styles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are currently two themes built on Poole:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://hyde.getpoole.com&quot;&gt;Hyde&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://lanyon.getpoole.com&quot;&gt;Lanyon&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Learn more and contribute on &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/poole&quot;&gt;GitHub&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;whats-included&quot;&gt;What’s included&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Poole is a streamlined Jekyll site designed and built as a foundation for building more meaningful themes. Poole, and every theme built on it, includes the following:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Complete Jekyll setup included (layouts, config, &lt;a href=&quot;/404.html&quot;&gt;404&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;/atom.xml&quot;&gt;RSS feed&lt;/a&gt;, posts, and &lt;a href=&quot;/about&quot;&gt;example page&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Mobile friendly design and development&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Easily scalable text and component sizing with &lt;code&gt;rem&lt;/code&gt; units in the CSS&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Support for a wide gamut of HTML elements&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Related posts (time-based, because Jekyll) below each post&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Syntax highlighting, courtesy Pygments (the Python-based code snippet highlighter)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Additional features are available in individual themes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;browser-support&quot;&gt;Browser support&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Poole and it’s themes are by preference a forward-thinking project. In addition to the latest versions of Chrome, Safari (mobile and desktop), and Firefox, it is only compatible with Internet Explorer 9 and above.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;download&quot;&gt;Download&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Poole is developed on and hosted with GitHub. Head to the &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/poole/poole&quot;&gt;GitHub repository&lt;/a&gt; for downloads, bug reports, and features requests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Example content</title>
   <link href="http://gamesketches.gitpages.io//2014/01/01/example-content/"/>
   <updated>2014-01-01T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://gamesketches.gitpages.io/2014/01/01/example-content</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;div class=&quot;message&quot;&gt;
  Howdy! This is an example blog post that shows several types of HTML content supported in this theme.
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cum sociis natoque penatibus et magnis &lt;a href=&quot;#&quot;&gt;dis parturient montes&lt;/a&gt;, nascetur ridiculus mus. &lt;em&gt;Aenean eu leo quam.&lt;/em&gt; Pellentesque ornare sem lacinia quam venenatis vestibulum. Sed posuere consectetur est at lobortis. Cras mattis consectetur purus sit amet fermentum.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Curabitur blandit tempus porttitor. Nullam quis risus eget urna mollis ornare vel eu leo. Nullam id dolor id nibh ultricies vehicula ut id elit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Etiam porta &lt;strong&gt;sem malesuada magna&lt;/strong&gt; mollis euismod. Cras mattis consectetur purus sit amet fermentum. Aenean lacinia bibendum nulla sed consectetur.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;inline-html-elements&quot;&gt;Inline HTML elements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;HTML defines a long list of available inline tags, a complete list of which can be found on the &lt;a href=&quot;https://developer.mozilla.org/en-US/docs/Web/HTML/Element&quot;&gt;Mozilla Developer Network&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To bold text&lt;/strong&gt;, use &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;To italicize text&lt;/em&gt;, use &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Abbreviations, like &lt;abbr title=&quot;HyperText Markup Langage&quot;&gt;HTML&lt;/abbr&gt; should use &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;abbr&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt;, with an optional &lt;code&gt;title&lt;/code&gt; attribute for the full phrase.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Citations, like &lt;cite&gt;— Mark otto&lt;/cite&gt;, should use &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;cite&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;del&gt;Deleted&lt;/del&gt; text should use &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;del&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;ins&gt;inserted&lt;/ins&gt; text should use &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;ins&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Superscript &lt;sup&gt;text&lt;/sup&gt; uses &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;sup&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt; and subscript &lt;sub&gt;text&lt;/sub&gt; uses &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;sub&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most of these elements are styled by browsers with few modifications on our part.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;heading&quot;&gt;Heading&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Vivamus sagittis lacus vel augue rutrum faucibus dolor auctor. Duis mollis, est non commodo luctus, nisi erat porttitor ligula, eget lacinia odio sem nec elit. Morbi leo risus, porta ac consectetur ac, vestibulum at eros.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;code&quot;&gt;Code&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cum sociis natoque penatibus et magnis dis &lt;code&gt;code element&lt;/code&gt; montes, nascetur ridiculus mus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-js&quot; data-lang=&quot;js&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;// Example can be run directly in your JavaScript console&lt;/span&gt;

&lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;// Create a function that takes two arguments and returns the sum of those arguments&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;kd&quot;&gt;var&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nx&quot;&gt;adder&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;new&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;Function&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&amp;quot;a&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&amp;quot;b&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&amp;quot;return a + b&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;);&lt;/span&gt;

&lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;// Call the function&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;nx&quot;&gt;adder&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;2&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;6&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;);&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;// &amp;gt; 8&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Aenean lacinia bibendum nulla sed consectetur. Etiam porta sem malesuada magna mollis euismod. Fusce dapibus, tellus ac cursus commodo, tortor mauris condimentum nibh, ut fermentum massa.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;gists-via-github-pages&quot;&gt;Gists via GitHub Pages&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Vestibulum id ligula porta felis euismod semper. Nullam quis risus eget urna mollis ornare vel eu leo. Donec sed odio dui.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;script src=&quot;https://gist.github.com/5555251.js?file=gist.md&quot;&gt; &lt;/script&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Aenean eu leo quam. Pellentesque ornare sem lacinia quam venenatis vestibulum. Nullam quis risus eget urna mollis ornare vel eu leo. Cum sociis natoque penatibus et magnis dis parturient montes, nascetur ridiculus mus. Donec sed odio dui. Vestibulum id ligula porta felis euismod semper.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;lists&quot;&gt;Lists&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cum sociis natoque penatibus et magnis dis parturient montes, nascetur ridiculus mus. Aenean lacinia bibendum nulla sed consectetur. Etiam porta sem malesuada magna mollis euismod. Fusce dapibus, tellus ac cursus commodo, tortor mauris condimentum nibh, ut fermentum massa justo sit amet risus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Praesent commodo cursus magna, vel scelerisque nisl consectetur et.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Donec id elit non mi porta gravida at eget metus.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Nulla vitae elit libero, a pharetra augue.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Donec ullamcorper nulla non metus auctor fringilla. Nulla vitae elit libero, a pharetra augue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Vestibulum id ligula porta felis euismod semper.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Cum sociis natoque penatibus et magnis dis parturient montes, nascetur ridiculus mus.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Maecenas sed diam eget risus varius blandit sit amet non magna.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cras mattis consectetur purus sit amet fermentum. Sed posuere consectetur est at lobortis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;dl&gt;
  &lt;dt&gt;HyperText Markup Language (HTML)&lt;/dt&gt;
  &lt;dd&gt;The language used to describe and define the content of a Web page&lt;/dd&gt;

  &lt;dt&gt;Cascading Style Sheets (CSS)&lt;/dt&gt;
  &lt;dd&gt;Used to describe the appearance of Web content&lt;/dd&gt;

  &lt;dt&gt;JavaScript (JS)&lt;/dt&gt;
  &lt;dd&gt;The programming language used to build advanced Web sites and applications&lt;/dd&gt;
&lt;/dl&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Integer posuere erat a ante venenatis dapibus posuere velit aliquet. Morbi leo risus, porta ac consectetur ac, vestibulum at eros. Nullam quis risus eget urna mollis ornare vel eu leo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;images&quot;&gt;Images&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Quisque consequat sapien eget quam rhoncus, sit amet laoreet diam tempus. Aliquam aliquam metus erat, a pulvinar turpis suscipit at.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://placehold.it/800x400&quot; alt=&quot;placeholder&quot; title=&quot;Large example image&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://placehold.it/400x200&quot; alt=&quot;placeholder&quot; title=&quot;Medium example image&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://placehold.it/200x200&quot; alt=&quot;placeholder&quot; title=&quot;Small example image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;tables&quot;&gt;Tables&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Aenean lacinia bibendum nulla sed consectetur. Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Name&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Upvotes&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Downvotes&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tfoot&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Totals&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;21&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;23&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tfoot&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Alice&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;10&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;11&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Bob&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;4&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;3&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Charlie&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;9&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nullam id dolor id nibh ultricies vehicula ut id elit. Sed posuere consectetur est at lobortis. Nullam quis risus eget urna mollis ornare vel eu leo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Want to see something else added? &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/poole/poole/issues/new&quot;&gt;Open an issue.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>What's Jekyll?</title>
   <link href="http://gamesketches.gitpages.io//2013/12/31/whats-jekyll/"/>
   <updated>2013-12-31T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://gamesketches.gitpages.io/2013/12/31/whats-jekyll</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://jekyllrb.com&quot;&gt;Jekyll&lt;/a&gt; is a static site generator, an open-source tool for creating simple yet powerful websites of all shapes and sizes. From &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/jekyll/jekyll/blob/master/README.markdown&quot;&gt;the project’s readme&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Jekyll is a simple, blog aware, static site generator. It takes a template directory […] and spits out a complete, static website suitable for serving with Apache or your favorite web server. This is also the engine behind GitHub Pages, which you can use to host your project’s page or blog right here from GitHub.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s an immensely useful tool. Find out more by &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/jekyll/jekyll&quot;&gt;visiting the project on GitHub&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 

</feed>
